nycerome.com 2005-12-31

# Rome hotels, online reservation of hotels in Rome, Italy

**Privacy policy**  
No personal informations (credit card details, booking activity, email address, etc.) is provided to anyone beyond the vendor that the costumer designate.  
Eur Travel by Real Time Sas and/or authorized third party to assemble personal data (name, e-mail etc.) and or/other informations (residence, nationality, etc.) inserted by the costumer when he makes an hotel booking or ask for informations by using nycerome.com.  
Credit Card informations are transmitted to the requested hotel, in order to complete the reservation. We can utilize the given e-mail and e-mail address to contact the costumer and send all the necessary informations regarding services and requested products.   
The security of the information given by the customer to us is very important; we utilize a cryptographic system (SSL) during the booking request and other measures to protect the costumer sensible data from loss, abuse and alteration. nyceRome includes links to other sites: this site is not responsible in any way for the actions and security of these third parties who do not share with us any information regarding the customer. 

**Conformably to the Italian privacy law**  
The personal data of the customer are registered by Eur Travel by Real Time Sas conformably to art. 10 of the Italian Law 675/96, only for the aim of utilizing the reservation system, other services requested by the customer or accomplishing the relevant communications/notices.   
Data will be given only to the addresses of the requests or reservations, to the hotels, or to a third party appointed to do this service in behalf of Eur Travel by Real Time Sas.  
The customer benefit from the rights of art. 13 Italian Law 675/96, furthermore the customer can in any moment request the cancellation of his data from the archive sending a simple written request, also by e-mail.   
Owner / holder and responsible of the collection, preservation and treatment of the data is Eur Travel by Real Time Sas, Via Viterbo 8, 00197, Rome, Italy  
The information presented on this page have a mere informative nature and do not constitute contractual bond, they do not give any legal power to the customer against Eur Travel by Real Time Sas except for what is foreseen by the Italian privacy law 675/96 .

* * *

**Abstract of the Privacy Law 675/96 (Italian Act 675/96)**   
Article 10  
The party concerned or the person by whom the personal data are collected must previously be informed in writing regarding:   
a) The aims and modalities of treatment to which the data are appointed  
b) The compulsory or optional nature of the data bestowal / granting  
c) The consequences of a possible refusal to reply  
d) The subjects or subjects' categories to whom data can be noticed and the divulgation sphere of the same data  
e) The rights of art. 13  
f) The name, denomination, or title and domicile, residence or the owner registered office and if appointed, of the person in charge.  
Information act on comma 1 can not comprehend the elements already known to the person who gives the data or of which the knowledge can interfere with the fulfillment of the public inspective function or of control, made for the pursue of the aims shown in art. 4, comma 1 letter e), and 14, comma 1 letter d).  
When the personal data are not gather up by the interested, the information act, comma 1, is given to the same interested person when he registers his personal data or if their communication is foreseen, not longer the first communication.  
The provision, noted in comma 3, does not apply when the information to the interested implies an utilization of means, which can be judged by the surety clearly out of proportion in respect of the defensive right, otherwise it disclose impossible by the surety judgment, otherwise when the data are used following a duty foreseen by the law, by an act of by the communitarian regulations.   
The same rule does not also apply when the data are used for the investigation development of art. 38 of the execution rules, coordination and fleeting rules of the penal procedure code, approved by the law decree 28th July 1989, n. 271, and further modifications, or however, in order to make worth of defend a right in judicial place, only if the data are treated exclusively for such scope and for the necessary period of time.
